Guide to the Duke Gardens Foundation records, 1912-2002 and undated
Duke University. University Archives
- Administrative Records, 1939-2002 and undated
  - Tour reservation schedules, April-May 1997 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Tour reservation schedules, October-December 1997 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Bovis - Building Evaluation reporting, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Hillsborough Township sign permit, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Main display schedule, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda - general administration, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Minutes of Managers Meetings, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Permits - New Jersey Office of Boiler and Pressure Vessel Compliance, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Public Service Electric and Gas Company - state electricity deregulation, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Request Forms for Purchase or Work Project exceeding $500.00, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Reports, Duke Gardens Foundation, statement of income, and main display schedule for gardens. 1997 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Daily tour numbers, October 1997-May 1998 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Automatic Communications Alarm Company, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Book stock requests, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Control sheets by month - cards, slides, reels, and viewers, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, clippings, and promotional materials regarding tours, 4 April 1998-5 April 1998, conducted by Somerset County's Heritage Trail Assocation, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Fire extinguishers, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Monthly ticket control sheets, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Notes of Tony Gsell and bills - Duke Gardens residence, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Notes of Tony Gsell - grounds and bills, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Ticket season control sheets, includes book stock request forms, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Information on Lewis Gitner Botanical Gardens, March 11, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Memorandum - orders over $500 from Parker, September 29, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Tour reservation schedules, January-March 1998 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Tour reservation schedules, April-May 1998 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Tour reservations schedules, October-December 1998 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - American Orchid Society book catalog, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Blue print for House #30 kitchen renovation - includes architectural record, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Lynn Brown of NJN Television, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Loeffels Waste Oil Removal Co., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Publicity material and order forms for NJN's "Gardens: Great and Small" video covering Duke Gardens, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Request Forms for Purchase or Work Project exceeding $500.00, 1998 (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Request Forms for Purchase or Work Project exceeding $500.00, 1998 (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Tropical plants - Finca La Vista Tropicals, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Display season schedules, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Tour reservations schedules, January-March 1999 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Tour reservations schedules, April-May 1999 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Tour reservations schedules, October-December 1999 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Request Form for Purchase or Work Order exceeding $500.00, 1999 (1 of 3) (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Request Form for Purchase or Work Order exceeding $500.00, 1999 (2 of 3) (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Request Form for Purchase or Work Order exceeding $500.00, 1999 (3 of 3) (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Tour schedule, October 1999-May 2000 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper and magazine articles about Duke Gardens, includes correspondence and color slides, 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Ashland Chemical - Drew Water Services, 1999-2001 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Tour reservations schedules, January-March 2000 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Tour reservations schedules, April-May 2000 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Maintenance Building - inventory blank forms, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Maintenance work request and order forms - House #30, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Maintenance work request and order forms - Orchid Range, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Motor pool work orders, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Park Department Work Request Forms, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Request Forms for Purchase or Work Project exceeding $500.00, 2000 (1 of 3) (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Request Forms for Purchase or Work Project exceeding $500.00, 2000 (2 of 3) (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Request Forms for Purchase or Work Project exceeding $500.00 (3 of 3) (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Work request forms, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Work request forms - greenhouses, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Work request form - House #30, January 2001 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Work request form - House #29, March 2001 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Certificate of Dissolution for Duke Gardens (copy). Date of dissolution authorized. November 13, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Notes - administrative phone calls missed and received, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Request Forms for Purchase or Work Project exceeding $500.00, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Telephone repair requests, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Work request forms - Orchid Range, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Work request forms, 2001-2002 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Work request forms - greenhouses, 2001-2002 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc., circuit descriptions, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Drawing, Griffinia hyacinthina flower, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Estimate for automated sprinkler system in the greenhouses, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Lecture notes regarding Duke Gardens operations, unsigned, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of specimens taken by former DGF employee, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Plants on loan - Woodstream, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Postcards of Phipps Conservatory in Pittsburgh and the Gardens at Niagra Falls, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Publicity copy drafts, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - The Illustrated Dictionary of Gardening: A Practical Encyclopedia of Horticulture, Parts 1, 2, and 5, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - The Illustrated Dictionary of Gardening: A Practical Encyclopedia of Horticulture, Parts 6, 7, and 9, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - The Illustrated Dictionary of Gardening: A Practical Encyclopedia of Horticulture, Parts 9, 10, and 13, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - The Illustrated Dictionary of Gardening: A Practical Encyclopedia of Horticulture, Parts 14, 17, and 18, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - The Illustrated Dictionary of Gardening: A Practical Encyclopedia of Horticulture, Parts 19, 20, and 22, undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Evening Tours Log, 1970-1976 (Oversize-box 34, Box 33)
  - Evening Tours Log, 1976-1977 (Oversize-box 34, Box 33)
  - Growing Area Tours Log, 1973 (Oversize-box 35, Box 33)
  - Tour Reservation Log, 1974 (Oversize-box 36, Box 33)
  - Tour Reservation Log, 1975 (Oversize-box 36, Box 33)
  - Tour Reservation Log, 1976 (Oversize-box 37, Box 33)
  - Tour Reservation Log, 1977 (Oversize-box 37, Box 33)
  - Tour Schedules, 1978 (Oversize-box 38, Box 33)
  - Tour Schedules, 1979 (Oversize-box 38, Box 33)
  - Tour Reservation Log, 1978 (Oversize-box 39, Box 33)
  - Tour Reservation Log, 1979 (Oversize-box 39, Box 33)
  - Tour Reservation Log, 1980 (Oversize-box 40, Box 33)
  - Tour Reservation Log, 1981 (Oversize-box 40, Box 33)
  - Visitor Registry, 1980 (Oversize-box 41, Box 33)
  - Tour Schedules, 1981 (Oversize-box 42, Box 33)
  - Tour Schedules, 1983 (Oversize-box 42, Box 33)
  - Tour Schedules, 1982 (Oversize-box 43, Box 33)
  - Visitor Registry, 1982 (Oversize-box 44, Box 33)
  - Visitor Registry, 1985 (Oversize-box 45, Box 33)
  - Visitor Registry, 1986 (Oversize-box 46, Box 33)
  - Visitor Registry, 1987 (Oversize-box 46, Box 33)
  - Visitor Registry, 1988 (Oversize-box 47, Box 33)
  - In and Out Log, 1988 (Oversize-box 47, Box 33)
  - Visitor Registry, 1989 (Oversize-box 48, Box 33)
  - Visitor Registry, 1990 (Oversize-box 48, Box 33)
  - In and Out Log, 1990 (Oversize-box 49, Box 33)
  - In and Out Log, 1991 (Oversize-box 49, Box 33)
  - Visitor Registry, 1991 (Oversize-box 50, Box 33)
  - Visitor Registry, 1992 (Oversize-box 50, Box 33)
  - Visitor Registry, 1993 (Oversize-box 51, Box 33)
  - Visitor Registry, 1994 (Oversize-box 51, Box 33)
  - Visitor Registry, 1995 (Oversize-box 52, Box 33)
  - Visitor Registry, 1996 (Oversize-box 52, Box 33)
  - Visitor Registry, 1997 (Oversize-box 53, Box 33)
  - Visitor Registry, 1998 (Oversize-box 53, Box 33)
  - Visitor Registry, 1999 (Oversize-box 54, Box 33)
  - Correspondence from the office of Robert Dingwall, 1958-1959 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation general correspondence and reports, 1958-1960 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation - Prentice Hall Corp. Systems, 1958-1964 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation statements, 1960-1962 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation accounting reports, 1960-1964 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Estimates, 1960-1965 (1 of 2) (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Estimates, 1960-1965 (2 of 2) (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Specifications - alterations and additions to Reception Center, 1961 Jul 3 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation general correspondence and reports, 1961-1964 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous invoices for Duke Gardens Foundation, 1962-1973 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence from the office of Robert Dingwall, 1963-1969 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Greenhouse reports, 1964-1968 (1 of 2) (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Greenhouse reports, 1964-1968 (2 of 2) (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Estimates, 1964-1969 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation general correspondence and reports, 1965-1971 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Plastic extruded, 1967 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Donations to Duke Gardens Foundation, 1968-1994 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation - Members, Directors and Officers as of June 30, 1973, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - DGF Tour Information and Publicity, 1973 and undated (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous reports on Duke Gardens Foundation, 1973-1984 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and related materials on potential for solar energy at Duke Gardens, 1975-1980 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous reports and correspondence regarding Duke Gardens Foundation (A. Searles), 1978-1981 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Orchid Update, 1991 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - "Lily the Duke Garden Cat" - Princeton Day School, 2000 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Plant card catalog, undated (1 of 4) (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Plant card catalog, undated (2 of 4) (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Plant card catalog, undated (3 of 4) (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Plant card catalog, undated (4 of 4) (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Variety of correspondence regarding administration of Duke Gardens Foundation, 1962-1981 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Rimmer letter regarding Al Shanosky, 1964 Sep 9 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, memoranda, and other materials related to Duke Gardens Foundation, 1966-1987 and undated (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence regarding purchase of bulbs from Electric Wax Candle Company, 1974, 1984 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Duke Gardens reservations - Saturday, Sunday and Holidays, 1978 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Activities performed at Duke Gardens Foundation, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Memorandum regarding free tours of SEAAC at Duke Gardens Foundation, 1993 Oct 4 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Photograph, Duke Gardens, Interior Garden and French Garden, 2004 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Photographs of Duke Gardens taken before dismantling, 2008 Dec 11 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation employee list, undated (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence related to Lord & Burnham agreement to renovate the Italian Garden, 1971-1974 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Administrative materials related to the Duke Gardens Foundation, 1980 and undated (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Catalog, "Furniture and Works of Art in The Elms Residence of the late Miss Julia A. Berwind", under the management of Parke-Bernet Galleries. Two statues on page 145 were purchased for Duke Gardens, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation, Inc. Board Book. Includes Certificate of Incorporation, 1958-1961 (Box 125)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation, Inc. Board Book, 1963-1970 (Box 125)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation, Inc. Board Book, 1971-1980 (Box 126)
- Financial Records, 1958-1993 (Box 126)
  A majority of the materials in this series are paid invoices and related correspondence for the numerous contractors and businesses providing services to the Duke Gardens Foundation. Invoices include purchases for cement, insecticides, plants, and manhole covers; services for woodworking, building renovations, electrical services, and scaffolding and equipment, and purchases for employment related services including job ads and temporary employment. Also included are transactions between Duke Gardens Foundation and Duke Farms for the use of equipment and workers. To a lesser degree, the series contains general ledgers and journals, which include information such as donations income, administrative and grounds expenses, and investments.
  For ease of use, the series is arranged by paid invoices and related correspondence, general ledgers and cashbooks and general financial. In each category, the materials are arranged chronologically and alphabetically thereunder.
  - Invoices paid, A-Z, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid - Greenhouse, 1958-1959 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid by Duke Farms for new greenhouse for orchid range, 1958 Nov-1959 May (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid - A, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid - B, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid - C, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid - D, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation Statements, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Invoices paid - E, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Invoices paid - F, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Invoices paid - G, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Invoices paid - H, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Invoices paid - Hospital Service Plan of NJ, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Invoices paid - I, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Invoices paid - J, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Invoices paid - K, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Invoices paid - L, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid - Lord & Burnham, 1959 (1 of 2) (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid - Lord & Burnham, 1959 (2 of 2) (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid - M, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid - N, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid - O, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid - P, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Petty Cash, 1959 (1 of 2) (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Petty Cash, 1959 (2 of 2) (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Invoices paid - R, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Invoices paid - S, 1959 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid - T, 1959 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid - U-V, 1959 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid - W, 1959 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid - A, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid - B, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid - C, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation Statements, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Invoices paid - D, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Invoices paid - E, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Invoices paid - F, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Invoices paid - G, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Invoices paid - H, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Invoices paid - Hoff's Electric Service, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Invoices paid - Hospital Service Plan of NJ, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Invoices paid - I, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Invoices paid - Insurance, 1959-1960 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Invoices paid - J, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Invoices paid - K, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid - L, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid - Lord & Burnham, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid - M, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid - N, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid - O, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid - P, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Petty Cash, 1960 (1 of 3) (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Petty Cash, 1960 (2 of 3) (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Petty Cash, 1960 (3 of 3) (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Invoices paid - R, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid - Raritan Valley Cooperative GLF Service, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid - Raritan Valley Plumbing Supply, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid - S, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid - Sargeant Bros., 1960 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid - Somerville Hardware Co., 1960 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid - Supreme Petroleum Co., 1960 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Invoices paid - T, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Invoices paid - U, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Invoices paid - V, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Invoices paid - W, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Invoices paid - X, Y, Z, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation Statements, 1962 Feb-1962 Dec (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - A, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Amerman Co., 1962 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Aneskewich, Edward P., 1962 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - B, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Bacorn, Dewitt, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Berman & Co., 1962 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Bothers, A.R., 1962 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Brewer, Elmer, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Buzby & Sons, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - C, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Consumers' Lumber & Supply Co., 1962 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - D, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Deluccia, Frank, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Duke Farms, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - E, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - F, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - G, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - H, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - H & E-lectric, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Hospital Service Plan of NJ, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Houdaille Construction Materials, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Houser Auto Supply, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - I, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - J, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - K, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - L, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - M, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Manpower, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - N, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - O, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Ostro's Camera Shop, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - P, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Pave-Rite, Inc., 1962 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - R, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Raritan Valley Hardware Co., 1962 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Raritan Valley Plumbing Supply Co., 1962 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Russell, Gerald S., 1962 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - S, 1962 (1 of 2) (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - S, 1962 (2 of 2) (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Somerset Plumbing Supply, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Sutton Tree Service, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - T, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Tectonic Associates, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Township of Hillsborough, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - U, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - V, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - W, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Y, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Duke Farms, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - A, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Aneskewich, Edward P., 1963 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Arcade Propane Gas, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - B, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Bacorn, Dewitt, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Berman & Co., 1963 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Brewer, Elmer, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Burns Detective Agency, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Buzby & Sons, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - C, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Cola (Pepsi), 1963 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Cooperative GLF Exchange, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - D, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Deluccia, Frank, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Duke Sales/Orchid miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - E, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - F, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - G, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - H, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - H & E-lectric Co., 1963 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Hospital Service Plan of NJ, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Houdaille Construction Materials, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Houser Auto Supply, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Hunterdon GLF Petroleum Coop. Inc., 1963 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Insurance, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - I, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - J, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - K, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - L, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - M, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Manpower, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - N, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - New Jersey Bell Telephone Co., 1963 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - O, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - P, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Petty Cash, 1963 (1 of 3) (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Petty Cash, 1963 (2 of 3) (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Petty Cash, 1963 (3 of 3) (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - R, 1963 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Raritan Valley Coop GLF Services, 1963 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Raritan Valley Plumbing Supply, 1963 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Raritan Valley Hardware Co., 1963 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Invoices paid and correspondence - Russell, Gerald S., 1963 (Box 68, Folder 7)